<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Monitoring Vault Server on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/monitoring/vault-server/</link><description>Recent content in Monitoring Vault Server on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/monitoring/vault-server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Grafana dashboard for Vault Server</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/monitoring/vault-server/grafana/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/monitoring/vault-server/grafana/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Visualize Vault server data using Grafana dashboard Grafana provides an elegant graphical user interface to visualize data. You can create beautiful dashboard easily with a meaningful representation of your Prometheus metrics.
If there is no grafana instance running on your cluster, then you can read this tutorial to deploy one.
Add Prometheus Data Source We have to add our Prometheus server prometheus-prometheus-0 as data source of grafana.</description></item><item><title>Monitor Vault Server using Builtin Prometheus Discovery</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/monitoring/vault-server/builtin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/monitoring/vault-server/builtin/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Monitor Vault server with builtin Prometheus The prometheus server is needed to configure so that it can discover endpoints of services. If a Prometheus server is already running in cluster and if it is configured in a way that it can discover service endpoints, no extra configuration will be needed.
If there is no existing Prometheus server running, read this tutorial to see how to create a builtin Prometheus server with appropriate configuration.</description></item><item><title>Monitor Vault Server using CoreOS Prometheus Operator</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/monitoring/vault-server/coreos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/monitoring/vault-server/coreos/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Monitoring Vault Server Using CoreOS Prometheus Operator The prometheus server is needed to configure so that it can discover endpoints of services. If a Prometheus server is already running in cluster and if it is configured in a way that it can discover service endpoints, no extra configuration will be needed.
If there is no existing Prometheus server running, read this tutorial to see how to install CoreOS Prometheus Operator.</description></item></channel></rss>