<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Concepts | Azure Secret Engine on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/azure-secret-engine/</link><description>Recent content in Concepts | Azure Secret Engine on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/azure-secret-engine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AzureAccessKeyRequest | Vault Secret Engine</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/azure-secret-engine/azureaccesskeyrequest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/azure-secret-engine/azureaccesskeyrequest/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
AzureAccessKeyRequest What is AzureAccessKeyRequest An AzureAccessKeyRequest is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition (CRD) which allows a user to request for Azure credentials in a Kubernetes native way. If an AzureAccessKeyRequest is approved, then the KubeVault operator will issue credentials using a Vault server and create a Kubernetes secret containing the Azure credentials. The secret name will be specified in status.secret.name field. The operator will also create appropriate ClusterRole and ClusterRoleBinding for the k8s secret.</description></item><item><title>AzureRole | Vault Secret Engine</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/azure-secret-engine/azurerole/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/azure-secret-engine/azurerole/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
AzureRole What is AzureRole An AzureRole is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition (CRD) which allows a user to create an Azure secret engine role in a Kubernetes native way.
When an AzureRole is created, the KubeVault operator configures a Vault role. A role may be set up with either an existing service principal or a set of Azure roles that will be assigned to a dynamically created service principal.</description></item></channel></rss>