<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Platform Guides | KubeVault on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/</link><description>Recent content in Platform Guides | KubeVault on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy Vault on Amazon EKS</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/eks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/eks/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Deploy Vault on Amazon EKS Here, we are going to deploy Vault in Amazon EKS using Vault operator. We are going to use AWS S3 bucket as Vault backend and awsKmsSsm unsealer mode for automatic unsealing the Vault.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a EKS cluster. If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have a cluster, create one from here. You can use eksctl command line tool to create EKS cluster easily.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Vault on Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/aks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/aks/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Deploy Vault on Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) Here, we are going to deploy Vault in AKS using Vault operator. We are going to use Azure Storage Container as Vault backend and azureKeyVault unsealer mode for automatic unsealing the Vault.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a AKS cluster. If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have a cluster, create one from here.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Vault on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE)</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/gke/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/gke/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Deploy Vault on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) Here, we are going to deploy Vault in GKE using Vault operator. We are going to use GCS bucket as Vault backend and googleKmsGcs unsealer mode for automatic unsealing the Vault.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a GKE cluster. If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have a cluster, create one from here.
Install Vault operator in your cluster following the steps here.</description></item><item><title>Manage External Vault using Vault Operator</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/external-vault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/external-vault/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Manage External Vault using Vault Operator You can manage external Vault (not deployed by Vault operator) by Vault operator. You can do following operations using Vault operator:
Manage Vault policy using VaultPolicy and VaultPolicyBinding. Guides can be found here.
Manage AWS secret engine using AWSRole and AWSAccessKeyRequest. Guides can be found here.
Manage PostgreSQL Database secret engine using PostgresRole and DatabaseAccessRequest.</description></item><item><title>Use a Vault Server with Multiple Kubernetes Clusters</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/multi-cluster-vault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/0.1.0/guides/platforms/multi-cluster-vault/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Use a Vault Server with Multiple Kubernetes Clusters In this tutorial, we are going to show how to use Vault operator in multiple Kubernetes clusters with a single Vault server.
To being with, we have created two GKE clusters.
We are going to install Vault operator in demo-cluster-1. We are going to set --cluster-name flag. This flag value will be used by Vault operator when creating resources in Vault.</description></item></channel></rss>