<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Concepts | Vault Policy on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/policy-crds/</link><description>Recent content in Concepts | Vault Policy on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/policy-crds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VaultPolicy | KubeVault Concepts</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/policy-crds/vaultpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/policy-crds/vaultpolicy/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
VaultPolicy What is VaultPolicy A VaultPolicy is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition (CRD) which represents Vault server policies in a Kubernetes native way.
When a VaultPolicy is created, the KubeVault operator will create a policy in the associated Vault server according to specification. If the VaultPolicy CRD is deleted, the respective policy will also be deleted from the Vault server.
VaultPolicy CRD Specification Like any official Kubernetes resource, a VaultPolicy object has TypeMeta, ObjectMeta, Spec and Status sections.</description></item><item><title>VaultPolicyBinding | KubeVault Concepts</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/policy-crds/vaultpolicybinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/policy-crds/vaultpolicybinding/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
VaultPolicyBinding What is VaultPolicyBinding A VaultPolicyBinding is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition (CRD) which binds Vault server policies to an auth method role in a Kubernetes native way.
When a VaultPolicyBinding is created, the KubeVault operator will create an auth role according to CRD (CustomResourceDefinition) specification. If the user deletes the VaultPolicyBinding CRD, then the respective role will also be deleted from Vault.
Auth method roles are associated with an authentication type/entity and a set of Vault policies.</description></item></channel></rss>