<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Platform Guides | KubeVault on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/</link><description>Recent content in Platform Guides | KubeVault on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy Vault on Amazon EKS</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/eks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/eks/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Deploy Vault on Amazon EKS Here, we are going to deploy Vault in Amazon EKS using KubeVault operator. We are going to use AWS S3 bucket as Vault backend and awsKmsSsm unsealer mode for automatically unsealing the Vault.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have an EKS cluster. If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have a cluster, create one from here. You can use eksctl command line tool to create EKS cluster easily.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Vault on Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/aks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/aks/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Deploy Vault on Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) Here, we are going to deploy Vault in AKS using KubeVault operator. We are going to use Azure Storage Container as Vault backend and azureKeyVault unsealer mode for automatically unsealing the Vault.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have an AKS cluster. If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have a cluster, create one from here.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Vault on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE)</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/gke/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/gke/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Deploy Vault on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) Here, we are going to deploy Vault in GKE using KubeVault operator. We are going to use GCS bucket as Vault backend and googleKmsGcs unsealer mode for automatically unsealing the Vault.
Before You Begin At first, you need to have a GKE cluster. If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have a cluster, create one from here.</description></item><item><title>Manage External Vault using KubeVault operator</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/external-vault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/external-vault/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Manage External Vault using KubeVault operator The KubeVault operator can manage policies and secret engines of Vault servers which are not provisioned by the KubeVault operator. These Vault servers can be running outside a Kubernetes cluster or running inside a Kubernetes cluster but provisioned using a Helm chart.
The KubeVault operator can perform the following operations for externally provisioned Vault servers:</description></item><item><title>Use a Vault Server with Multiple Kubernetes Clusters</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/multi-cluster-vault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/guides/platforms/multi-cluster-vault/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Use a Vault Server with Multiple Kubernetes Clusters In this tutorial, we are going to show how to use KubeVault operators in multiple Kubernetes clusters against a shared Vault server.
To being with, we have created two GKE clusters.
We are going to install KubeVault operator in demo-cluster-1 using Helm 3. We are going to set --cluster-name flag. This flag value will be used by KubeVault operator when creating resources in Vault.</description></item></channel></rss>