<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Concepts | KubeVault on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/</link><description>Recent content in Concepts | KubeVault on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>KubeVault Concepts</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/architecture/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
Architecture KubeVault operator is composed of the following controllers:
A Vault Server controller that deploys Vault in Kubernetes clusters. It also injects unsealer and stastd exporter as sidecars to perform unsealing and monitoring respectively.
An Auth controller that enables auth methods in Vault.
A Policy controller that manages Vault policies and also binds Vault policies with Kubernetes service accounts.</description></item><item><title>KubeVault Concepts</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/</guid><description>Concepts Concepts help you learn about the different parts of KubeVault and the abstractions it uses.
What is KubeVault? Overview. Provides an introduction to KubeVault operator, including the problems it solves and its use cases. Operator architecture. Provides a high-level illustration of the architecture of the KubeVault operator. Vault Server Secret Engines Vault Policies AppBinding Introduces a way to specify connection information, credential, and parameters that are necessary for communicating with an app or service.</description></item><item><title>What is KubeVault</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/what-is-kubevault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/concepts/what-is-kubevault/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
KubeVault What is KubeVault KubeVault operator is a Kubernetes controller for HashiCorp Vault. Vault is a tool for secrets management, encryption as a service, and privileged access management. Deploying, maintaining, and managing Vault in Kubernetes could be challenging. KubeVault operator eases these operational tasks so that developers can focus on solving business problems.
Why use KubeVault KubeVault operator makes it easy to deploy, maintain and manage Vault servers in Kubernetes.</description></item></channel></rss>