<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference | KubeVault CLI on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/reference/cli/</link><description>Recent content in Reference | KubeVault CLI on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/reference/cli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vault</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/reference/cli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/reference/cli/</guid><description>vault KubeVault cli by AppsCode
Synopsis KubeVault cli by AppsCode
Options --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups. --cache-dir string Default HTTP cache directory (default &amp;quot;/home/runner/.kube/http-cache&amp;quot;) --certificate-authority string Path to a cert file for the certificate authority --client-certificate string Path to a client certificate file for TLS --client-key string Path to a client key file for TLS --cluster string The name of the kubeconfig cluster to use --context string The name of the kubeconfig context to use -h, --help help for vault --insecure-skip-tls-verify If true, the server's certificate will not be checked for validity.</description></item><item><title>Vault Approve</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/reference/cli/vault_approve/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/reference/cli/vault_approve/</guid><description>vault approve Approve request
Synopsis Approve request
vault approve [flags] Options -f, --filename strings Filename, directory, or URL to files identifying the resource to update -h, --help help for approve -k, --kustomize string Process the kustomization directory. This flag can't be used together with -f or -R. -R, --recursive Process the directory used in -f, --filename recursively. Useful when you want to manage related manifests organized within the same directory.</description></item><item><title>Vault Deny</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/reference/cli/vault_deny/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/reference/cli/vault_deny/</guid><description>vault deny Deny request
Synopsis Deny request
vault deny [flags] Options -f, --filename strings Filename, directory, or URL to files identifying the resource to update -h, --help help for deny -k, --kustomize string Process the kustomization directory. This flag can't be used together with -f or -R. -R, --recursive Process the directory used in -f, --filename recursively. Useful when you want to manage related manifests organized within the same directory.</description></item><item><title>Vault Version</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/reference/cli/vault_version/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v2020.07.09-beta.0/reference/cli/vault_version/</guid><description>vault version Prints binary version number.
Synopsis Prints binary version number.
vault version [flags] Options --check string Check version constraint -h, --help help for version --short Print just the version number. Options inherited from parent commands --alsologtostderr log to standard error as well as files --analytics Send analytical events to Google Analytics (default true) --as string Username to impersonate for the operation --as-group stringArray Group to impersonate for the operation, this flag can be repeated to specify multiple groups.</description></item></channel></rss>