<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Concepts | GCP Secret Engine on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/gcp-secret-engine/</link><description>Recent content in Concepts | GCP Secret Engine on Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/gcp-secret-engine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GCPAccessKeyRequest | Vault Secret Engine</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/gcp-secret-engine/gcpaccesskeyrequest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/gcp-secret-engine/gcpaccesskeyrequest/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
GCPAccessKeyRequest What is GCPAccessKeyRequest An GCPAccessKeyRequest is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition (CRD) which allows a user to request for GCP credentials in a Kubernetes native way. If an GCPAccessKeyRequest is approved, then the KubeVault operator will issue credentials using a Vault server and create a Kubernetes secret containing the GCP credentials. The secret name will be specified in status.secret.name field. The operator will also create appropriate ClusterRole and ClusterRoleBinding for the k8s secret.</description></item><item><title>GCPRole | Vault Secret Engine</title><link>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/gcp-secret-engine/gcprole/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubevault.com/docs/v0.3.0/concepts/secret-engine-crds/gcp-secret-engine/gcprole/</guid><description>New to KubeVault? Please start here.
GCPRole What is GCPRole A GCPRole is a Kubernetes CustomResourceDefinition (CRD) which allows a user to create a GCP secret engine role in a Kubernetes native way.
When a GCPRole is created, the KubeVault operator configures a Vault roleset. The rolesets determine the permissions that Service Account credentials generated by Vault will have on GCP resources. If the user deletes the GCPRole CRD, then the respective role will also be deleted from Vault.</description></item></channel></rss>